Is it real?
Yes.
It's said to be from Dad to Mum.
Why have you got it?
Your grandfather gave it to your grandmother
before he left Spain.
She was pregnant with me-
-and never saw him again.
It's lovely.
I never thought I'd touch  a real diamond.
-Can I try it on?
-Yes.
-It's yours now, darling.
-Really?
I don't know. Mama always
wore it on this finger.
She said it wasn't real.
Your mama never heard that sound.
What sound?
That scares the owls away.
I saw that movie too.
Don't you believe me?
Before, there was nothing here.
Just water. Salt water.
Do you know what that sounded  like?
And the wind.
And both together?
What's that over there?
When did the symptoms start?
I don't know...months ago.
You can get dressed.
Couldn't you have come sooner?
It didn't hurt like this before.
A nurse is coming to take a blood sample.
Why don't you get started?
What's keeping you here?
-Did they tell you about the accident?
-Did you hear something?
I only heard Luis.
-The boy farthest away...
-Luis.
Luis is OK.
I helped him further.
He told me he was sorry
and asked to be forgiven...
...for stealing a watch.
Who do you think you are?
You're a disgrace. You know nothing.
You come here and just lie to us.
-My son was no thief.
-Let me explain...
Go! - Luis, tell him to go.
Show a bit of respect for our son.
He asked after you.
Tell him I'll look in in the morning.
Hi.
-Dad, I tried to ring you.
-I'm a bit late, sorry.
Get your bag. Are you right?
Thanks for the help, Lili.
Five o'clock tomorrow, OK?
Say 'bye to Lili.
-And Li.
-'Bye!
Fish is yucky.
We all eat the same.
What do you want then?
A hamburger and chips...
...and a chocolate milkshake.
Perfect.
And the lady?
Fried egg with sausage-
-and a potato omelette
with cream and cinnamon.
A hamburger.
And look at all the chips.
Chips here and chips there.
And a big chocolate milkshake.
What will the young lady have?
-Fried eggs.
-Fried eggs...
-With sausage.
-Sausage...
And a potato omelette.
-Potato omelette...
-with cream and cinnamon.
Everything as requested.
-What did you get for lunch?
-Rice with chicken.
Daddy, did you know-
-that if a spacesuit got a hole in it, it'd explode?
Tomorow I'll ask Lili to give you something else.
-It isn't Lili who does the food.
-So I'll tell Jung.
It's because of the gravity.
Stop kicking the table, Mateo.
Don't shove so much food into your mouth.
I've told you a thousand times.
A thousand times.
Don't be disgusting.
Put it back in your mouth.
Food in your mouth, Mateo.
Once more!
Now!
-Do you want any more milk?
-No.
Stop.
Leave the table
and go to your room.
Your supposed to go to your room,
not wash your plate.
What is it?
I've peed in my pants.
I'll wash them in the morning, Daddy.
Yes?
Wait a sec.
Can you turn that down?
Turn down the music and stop singing.
Yes, I'm here.
Sorry about that.
Yes, the cemetery rang again.
No, they're building a gallery.
Right over Dad.
They've offered good money.
They're offering good money.
They fix up about the coffin and so forth.
It's a good offer.
There's nothing you can do
to stop it.
We should have him cremated.
OK, we'll do it then.
Yes, OK, I'll call you.
OK, next week.
Look after yourself.
Talk to you later.
-Who's being cremated?
-Nobody.
Don't lie.
I'll give you a Thai massage.
Who?
-If you don't tell me...
-It's my dad!
We're cremating him.
-Which of you is most like your dad?
-I don't know.
I don't remember how he looked.
Give me a kiss.
I'm going.
I gotta go.
Stop it.
What the fuck are you doing?
Fucking pig!
She's sick in the head.
Where are the others?
I met Cchinaza on the way here.
-Where?
-In El Fondo.
I sent that bugger back.
Where Ccheikh and Mamadou?
You gotta keep a check on them,
otherwise we're stuffed.
I've said before.. they can't sell here.
It's off limits.
Understand?
Do you understand what I'm saying?
No one buys bugger all down there.
I also heard you've started dealing.
Boys, pack up, they're coming.
Mind the cops.
It's time to blow.
I got something to show you.
Home at my place.
Your place? Heavens...
It's stuck.
Can't open it.
Thanks, lge.
No sense in dropping the price
if nobody wants them.
Are they all the same?
Most of them.
This month's been a disaster.
You gotta talk to the Chinese.
Maybe I can get some umbrellas.
Fuck that.
There's fuck-all rain around here.
Yeah, you're right there.
-Can you get the kid to sleep?
-You'd think there was no one here.
A bit of quiet.
I've got guests.
Who's done this?
Is it you?
Who did this shit? Is this your handbag?
We're getting nowhere with pirate stuff for cash.
It's now or never.
20 building workers
at 1300 euro each...
That's a lot of money.
-I gotta think about that.
-We're stuffed with all your ideas.
We're losing the contract with Mendoza.
The workers then?
Will they go on making this shit?
I don't know what you're talking about
but we gotta do something, and quickly.
I don't think I'll go on selling shit.
-The idiot must be good at something.
-The idiot's done a lot more.
That's for your friend in the police.
Did you talk to Mendoza?
yes. My brother has a contact
in a building site in Badalona.
They need a lot of workers right now.
How much money in it?
How much?
That's nothing to laugh about, Hai.
How much is it?
What's up with you?
It's sensitive and I have family.
We aren't home in China.
Otherwise you better fucking-well learn African.
You better talk to your people too
and get them to calm down.
That's what I pay you for.
Listen, Uxbal.
We've known each other quite a while now.
But next time you stuff up, you're finished.
Got it?
Understood?
OK, let them know.
For October and November.
Next time they pay late, I put them inside.
Got it?
Or shall I translate?
-Daddy's home.
-Mummy picked us up barefoot.
I took my shoes off, too.
-Well?
-Well what?
-Why weren't you home?
-I can't be two places at once.
Mummy's making spaghetti.
Turn off the TV.
Sit down and eat.
Why is the shower on?
You don't have one ironed shirt.
Good way to iron, eh?
Come and eat.
Lili rang, she was upset.
We agreed you should tell me
if you fetched the children.
Sorry... a customer cancelled.
So call me on my mobile.
Will you have some omelette?
It's with apple slices.
Just like the potato one,
but softer and sweet.
-Aren't you eating?
-No, I'm not hungry.
Miguel's daughter said they were out in the car yesterday-
-when a motorbike overtook them going like a goddamned maniac.
So Miguel yelled out:
"Hope you die!"
Five minutes later they saw
the motorbike lying on the road-
-and the rider was a pulp
in a pool of blood.
Miguel was so shocked
that he drove to the hospital.
I don't understand why.
If someone did that to me...
Quiet. Marambra, that's enough.
If you could stop talking,
maybe you'd get hungry.
Do me a favour...put that cigarette out.
And take your foot off the table when we're eating.
Do you want to stay and watch a movie after, Mummy?
It's late, sweetie.
If I can't talk, how do I get you
not to include them at funerals?
That's why Mateo's still wetting his bed.
I haven't had them for ages.
That's not what they say.
Just because you have custody...
Do you come to hit your kids or question them?
Mamma, the spaghetti tastes nothing.
-You've still nearly eaten it all up.
-Off you go.
Go on.
Let's at least eat in peace.
Best I leave.
See you darling.
Enjoy yourself sweetie.
Marambra...
Sorry. You did good.
Did good?
Yeah.
Fuck what you think of me.
I'm not a dog.
You've turned the kids against me
No, Marambra, you did that yourself.
It's like it pisses you off to see me happy.
Only with you is it hard to be myself
and feel good..
Do you remember where you lived
last time you felt good?
Do you want me to remind you?
You don't need to remind me.
Why are you laughing?
I laugh at anything.
And I like to see people smile.
I'm happy if I'm happy and
down if I'm down.
I just wanted......
I love you.
I said I loved you.
Yes, me too.
You wouldn't have some money on you?
Haven't you got any more?
No.
Now that you're selling the grave.
Who told you that?
Tito.
When did you talk to him?
Please don't start. I gave him a
massage. He had a backache.
It's not a grave, it's a niche.
But...
No one told me I was obliged to fast.
And...
...it might be a technical error.
No, I'll complain.
Fasting is just a formality.
How's it coming along?
Excuse me?
How...
I've gotta know what happened.
It depends on how your body reacts to chemotherapy.
In your case it's gone a long time-
and it has metatasted from the prostate
to the skeleton and liver.
Which means...
But how long?
Roughly how long?
With medical treatment
you can keep your lifestyle-
-for a couple of months.
Months?
Daddy, I've learnt to do a trick.
Think of a country that starts with D.
Daddy, look at me.
Ready?
Yes.
Then think of an animal that starts with L.
Hippopotamus doesn't start with L.
Are you ready?
Yep.
You thought of
leeches in Denmark.
How did you know that?
Daddy, how do you spell ""beautiful""?
-Like it sounds.
-With an i?
Biutiful.
No, that's OK, don't be scared.
Just fetch the kids and take them home.
I don't know.
Til i get out.
In a couple of days, probably.
It's getting tough.
We close down the handbags
and copy movies.
You were right.
The building side is lucrative.
The building workers can keep going at Mendoza's.
Pay the ones we agreed on.
You won't regret it
We're helping them.
And it's safer for us.
There's a lot of money to be made.
Uxbal asked me for money
for the stoves in the warehouse.
I don't want anyone to freeze in the cellar.
OK, I'll see what I can do.
Where are you going?
I've got to go home.
Are you going to fight about a nigger?
How much was the bail?
I'll pay you back as soon as I can.
Forget it.
I'll take it from the money they give us for Dad's niche.
Has it been fixed up?
We just gotta fill in some forms from the cemetery
and we get the money.
But first we gotta cremate him.
After that we can do what we want.
We can bury him with Mum's ashes and save money.
Look at these things.
Careful, they're Dad's papers.
How's it going with the Chinese on the building site?
Mendoza is totally crapped off.
Most of them know nothing about building.
None of them speak Spanish
and they all look the same.
Have you told Marambra
about the cemetery?
No.
Hmm...
She rang me a while ago.
She rang me looking for you, or something.
But I didn't say anything to her.
I haven't seen her for ages.
Uxbal?
Take this.
That's not necessary.
I gotta know what my son said.
The day before the accident we had a row.
That was the last I...
Your son went off peacefully.
He was scared, so I helped him.
He talked about your watch
and where he'd hidden it.
Where?
Behind a leg of his bed.
Yes.
I'm very sorry. Really.
Who is it?
It's me.
I expected you tomorrow
I was in the area and...
Come in.
Thanks for the help with the kids
I was thinking I could take them now...
Quiet.
The kids are asleep.
What did you tell them?
That you were at your brother's.
Something about your work..
I'll pick them up in the morning
before they go to school, OK?
You're welcome to stay.
I can put on coffee or tea.
There's wine, too.
Don't look at me like that.
I haven't started drinking.
I opened it for a friend.
Remember my friend Laura?
Cheers.
Tack.
Did they hurt you?
No, I'm OK.
Ana told me about something she dreamt.
You had come home to the flat
and the bedroom was full of sand.
I asked her where Mateo was.
She said she didn't know.
But she believed he was buried under the sand.
Why are you going?
Stay.
I think you'll see me differently.
I don't think it's a good idea.
We both know what will happen.
There's room for everyone here.
From the kitchen you get a glimpse of the sea.
We can have breakfast together like we used to.
I can make toast for you...
-Be quiet a moment.
-The children need me.
The can't wake up to a new father every weekend.
You always come out with that crap.
It's not just about the kids.
I need you.
I haven't had a relapse in five months.
Give me a chance, darling.
You've said that a hundred times.
I haven't had a turn for ages.
It's different now, I promise.
Are you taking those tablets?
You got me to stop taking them
so I could breastfeed Mateo.
You're obsessed with those damned pills.
The doctor said you had to...
The doctor says anything to get rid of me.
None of that shit is going to cure my depression.
I'm trying with a lightbox now.
With a what?
A lightbox. It's terrific.
And much cheaper than medicine.
Can I show you?
You see?
It really is terrific.
I started a couple of months ago.
I feel better than ever.
But not like before.
It's different now.
I feel normal.
Like everyone else.
No, stop it Marambra.
No, cut it out...
Stop.
It's OK.
You're really tired.
-Besides, I'm getting old.
-No...no...what are you talking about?
That's me.
At the police station...
...couldn't I stop thinking...
...about coming back to
you and the kids again.
The kids and I need...
Do you remember the time we fucked
in the little cloakroom?
I'd just come to Barcelona
and you greeted me at the drycleaners
You took me in the cloakroom.
The owner caught us...
Up you get!
It's six-thirty.
There's bread and tea out there.
Get moving!
I'm always getting into all kinds of crap.
There are four underage minors.
I don't pay in advance.
If we get inspected, where will I hide
so many damned Chinese?
It's our only condition, Mendoza.
I don't pay a cent til I know I've got something
That's how we always do it.
Right, Uxbal?
A week on trial.
Half of them are sick and frozen.
They've never even seen a drill.
It doesn't help cut costs.
The costs?
OK.
Then you can go and hire
unionised construction workers.
When you've worked it out, ring me.
-When do you need the money?
-A week from today.
Stop looking like a scared Chinaman..
I'll pay for next week.
But then I'll have the papers latest on Friday.
Ok, OK.
On Anas birthday...
could the four of us go to the country?
Only at the weekend.
-Sure. Where to?
-Dunno.
The Pyrenees.
The kids have never seen snow.
They've never been out of this part of town.
We can camp.
No, I'd rather have a dog, a little dog
No, darling. They poo all day
and cost a fortune.
Travelling's much more fun.
Give me a bit.
I gotta taste it.
-What are you doing, Marambra?
-Do you want to taste it?
Use your spoon. Don't do that...
You're disgusting.
-Good, eh?
-Wanna try?
Do it.
Stick your hand in.
Once more.
-Isn't that great?
-Stop it.
What are you grumbling about?
Or don't you remember when you proposed to me?
What'd he do?
If you're gonna tell the story
tell about the look you gave me.
You and your look.
I hadn't seen you yet.
-Hadn't you ever seen me?
-I'm telling this, not you.
The day I met your dad
at a party he said-
-that I had the most beautiful nose he had ever seen.
And obviously I believed him.
Then he took my hand
to read my future.
He said that I'd get married
to a completely hopeless man-
-but that I'd be
truly loved.
Who knows how many birds he'd
used that on, but it worked with me.
He said that if I let go of his hand
it wouldn't come true.
And straightaway,
befrore I knew what was happening-
-he pulled my hand towards his nose-
-and shoved my finger up his nostril.
He dug out a booger
and lay it in my hand-
-and said that I'd always have
part of him with me.
A black hairy piece of snot.
It was disgusting.
So what are you whining about?
It's not true.
Would you believe I'd do something like that?
Whadda you want?
Have you come to beg forgiveness?
Money?
Don't give me any frigging money.
Say sorry to them too.
Just seeing you... if you hadn't had kids I'd have killed you.
They knew what they were doing.
They were illegals and they pushed drugs.
Ekweme and the others knew they couldn't be here.
The police won't allow it.
Understand?
Take the fucking money.
Me?
What'll I do with my kid?
Dunno. Dunno.
Here, drink this.
How are things with your wife?
OK. Better.
-And the children?
-The kids are fine.
And you?
You're dying.
Looks like it.
Spit.
How's life looking?
Are you prepared to leave it?
Yes, I think so.
I'm working on it.
You think so?
You've got to be sure.
Get your life in order.
Leave nothing undone.
I don't want to die, Bea.
I'm afraid
to leave the kids in the lurch.
Do you believe that it's you
who looks after the children?
Don't be naive, Uxbal.
The Universe looks after them.
Yes, but the universe doesn't pay the rent.
When I was Ana's age-
-my mum died.
I scarcely remember her.
My dad died without me ever meeting him.
That won't happen with my kids.
Tell them.
Tell them everything.
We know the dead'll never be in peace
if they're in debt to the living.
Why is this happening to me?
Is it punishment?
You can give up and let go-
-or hang on like stupid people do.
It's a long, strenuous journey, Uxbal.
Death is not the end, you know that.
I won't die, Bea.
No.
Yes, you will die.
I see it
and there's nothing I can do.
Put your life in order, Uxbal.
That's all that matters.
Chemo's poison.
What did you have for breakfast?
Milk coffee.
You've always been a handsome boy.
Remember what I said
the day we met?
That we got our free gift-
-so we'll pass it on.
Here.
When it's necessary,
give them to the children.
-What is it?
-For protection.
When you leave them-
-give them one each.
He said it felt like
a sea of mud inside him.
And his eyes felt like jelly-
-and his hair burnt.
Everybody up. It's 6.30.
-How many stoves did Uxbal bring?
-Six.
How's Ana?
Hi, Lili.
How're things?
I hope the stoves'll stop you from freezing.
Ana feels fine.
She wants to meet you.
We've moved in with her mother
.... she misses you.
I miss her too.
She loves to play with Li.
Uxbal, Hai wants to talk to you.
-See you, Lili.
-'Bye. Say goodbye.
Not one more day.
If you want to have them sew 16 hours
a day and exploit them as
-Exploit them?
-Yes, exploit them.
D'you know how much they earn in China?
Half a dollar a day.
Millions of Chinese'd suck my cock
every morning to be here
You forget I negotiated
a salary for each worker.
And I can see down there they're obviously getting fuck-all.
But I don't give a stuff about that.
Just give me my share, like we agreed.
Agreed to what?
You fucking piece of rotten meat!
It's my money, you cunt!
It's mine!
It's my money for fuck's sake!
Mine!
Fucking blood-sucker.
If you don't starve to death it's due to me.
If the Chinese have work
it's thanks to me.
If you two aren't locked up
If you don't give me half
of Mendozas money, I swear I'll...
What'll you do?
Who d'you think you are?
You turn everything to your own advantage
Uxbal...
They're putting me out in the morning.
You gotta stay at Samuel's.
-We're not staying without you.
-Samuel's a Spaniard...
Samuel's Senegalese like me.
We go back with you.
We'll be together again.
We're still young.
Stay.
Stay here at his place
and go on studying.
Work at the chicken factory again.
I send money to you.
Even if I chop off a million chicken heads-
-we can never afford a house here.
We don't belong here.
Why would you go back
to Senegal?
There's no work at all.
A man from the police came.
He said we're all being evicted.
Everyone. They gave us til Monday.
Uxbal 'll fix it.
I trust him.
I've already spoken to him.
Let him help us.
Hi.
Why're you looking like that?
What's happened to you?
Why'd you do it?
You needn't 've gone overboard.
Is that why you asked me to come?
To scold me?
What could've I done?
They do what the fuck they want.
What were you thinking?
Were you the only one who didn't know
they were drug pushers?
I warned you Uxbal.
We had to stop the niggers.
The money is not enough for everyone.
Should I live on my miserable salary?
Or will you steal from me?
They're being pushed out.
There are women with little kids...
-You aren't Mother Teresa.
-You know what I mean.
It's you who exploit them
so don't give us that shit.
I don't exploit them.
I help them get a job.
For money, like all the others.
-Want something?
-No thanks.
Do you remember Victor, Julia's son?
He moved to Murcia to train tigers
in a circus. He gave them food.
They danced for him
and licked his face.
I saw the show
with my daughter.
She wanted to bring a tiger home
They seemed to love him.
The other month
I met his mum.
A tiger had torn off a piece
of his face and killed him.
He gave them food every day.
Every day for six years.
But he made a mistake.
It's dangerous
to trust a starving man.
'Specially if his kids are starving too.
-What's that got to do with anything?
-What the fuck are you on about?
You gotta help Ekweme.
He's being kicked out. You gotta help me.
I'm not an MP.
I can't help you.
I can't go on playing I'm the UN.
I've got a daughter to look after.
D'you understand?
Be careful, Uxbal.
Or take an Alka Seltzer.
Chinese food can be very strong.
There are so many of those yellow bastards-
-that in the end they'll have the best ham
and we'll get to eat rice.
Daddy, did you know-
-that when owls die
they cough up a fur-ball?
No, I didn't know that.
Not so loud, you'll wake up Mummy.
Daddy, is mummy mad at us?
No.
Who's that?
-Your grandfather.
-Let me see.
That was the last photo taken of him
before he went off.
My mum always kept it in her purse.
Where'd he go to?
To Mexico.
-He didn't just go, he fled.
-Why'd he flee?
'cause your grandfather
couldn't keep his mouth shut.
At that time Franco persecuted and executed people
who couldn't keep their mouth shut.
When he was 20 he fled from Spain
so as not to die-
-but he died anyway 2 weeks later in Mexico
from a lung inflammation.
Do you love him a lot?
I don't know.
I never met him.
Not having a dad sucks.
When are we going up to see the snow?
Mummy said we're taking the train.
-Bags a window-seat.
-OK.
If we're going up to the snow-
-you gotta build up your strength
'cause there are tons of things to do.
Sleeping time.
Careful, It's heavy.
Fuck it, it's sealed with zinc.
Pass me the hammer and chisel.
Fuck, he's embalmed.
We take it as it is.
...placed the remains
of Mateo Gama Fernandez-
-in department 27
Saint Joseph year 1966.
Wonderful. Everything in order.
Your father died in Mexico.
Therefore he was embalmed
before being sent back here by sea.
I'm telling you this because the formaldehyde really works-
-and cremation can take a long time.
The body's driven
to Montjuic crematorium.
I suppose you'll want an urn.
These are his belongings.
They were in the coffin.
Can we see the body?
If you want, but people tend not to....
But if you wish
I'll call Montjuic right away.
Tony, please open the bag for identification.
Sorry, the door was open.
I'm coming now.
Sometimes the fridge hums-
-but if you give it a bang it'll stop.
There's hot water-
-but it's best to shower after 10 o'clock. OK??
I think that's everything.
Kids' room.
If you like you can be in here.
The rent is paid for the next few months.
Fuck...
Are you...
Are you OK?
I didn't know you did massage customers
in the middle of the night.
You scared me.
You should see the sky.
It's full of stars.
It's a damned nuisance that ants
always come in here.
Ana said you caught them by smoking
and the mattress caught on fire.
-Where have you been?
-Can't I have a bit of fun?
Not with 2 children alone at home-
-who don't know where you are.
And dressed like that.
So it's my fault?
Now I gotta ask your permission to be Mummy.
That's what happens
when a seven year old smokes.
Things start to burn.
Or didn't you know Mateo smoked?
You can't leave them, nor can you throw
a burning mattress out the window-
-and make them carry it up.
He's only seven.
But he can already hurt others
like he was 40.
He wanted to open the fridge ...
...with wet feet.
And he called me a whore.
The more love I give him-
-the more he calls me nasty names.
He said it was my fault
that we separated.
Did you hit him?
No.
Yes you did.
It's the only way he'll learn.
I bought the train tickets.
Four seats in first class.
I found a cute B&B
where we can spend the night.
The kids are so looking forward to the trip.
They talk about the Pyrenees-
-like they were Disneyland.
My darling one, what you see ou there are not stars.
It's your nervous system.
You could at least show you care.
We're ruined.
Finished.
We could have...
Shut up. It was your idea.
What's happened? Where are they?
-Where are they?
-You fucking piece of shit!
-You fucking murderer!
-Shut up!
-It was your idea too.
-We gotta scram.
-I don't wanna end up in jail.
-No one ever does.
Where are they?
Down there in the cellar.
We gotta decide what to do
with the one that's alive.
There's one that's alive?
There were two, but we couldn't...
One of them died.
Could be seen as suicide.
Promise me no one will know anything.
I'll give you all the money you need.
Just say how much.
Help me, help me!.
What are you doing?
Help me!
Uxbal, leave her alone.
She's already dead.
What'll we do?
You gotta help me.
I don't know.
Lock the goddamned warehouse.
Hang on, Marambra.
Dear Marambra, listen to me.
Listen to me.
Take the train this evening,
and we'll see in the morning.
Don't change the plan.
Don't change a fucking thing.
Take the kids
and go to the Pyrenees
Tell Ana I'm sorry,
but we'll have her birthday party when she comes home.
I tried to pray, but I don't know
who I should pray to.
Haven't you slept at all?
Out with it.
I bought the damned stoves
because they were cheapest.
Because I needed
the goddamned money.
I knew the stoves were rejects.
It's my fault, Bea.
All my fault...
They're all dead.
25 people, Bea.
There were women there.
And children...
Lili was there.
I wanted to ask her to forgive me,
but she was already dead.
I don't know if I'm going to the police.
I'm really frightened...
It was an accident, Uxbal.
It's OK.
You know what you must do, Uxbal.
Go and find them-
-and beg their forgiveness.
No, not that...
Not that...
Tito...
Where's the prodigal son.
What's up with you?
I've been trying to get hold of you.
I left a thousand messages.
Why don't you answer when I call?
Come here.
This is my out-of-reach brother.
What will you have to drink?
-Dunno.
-Cclara!
Mendoza went ballistic.
He nearly cut my balls off.
Cclara, give me one...two Jack Daniel's.
None of the Chinese came to work.
These sort of delays cost a fortune.
-What happened?
-There was a problem, Tito.
What the hell?
Why didn't you come to me?
Because... I don't know.
Come here, Cclarita.
Drink, we'll discuss this in the morning.
Hang on...
I've got to talk to you, Tito.
Here you gotta scream
or be on top of one another.
Look at her there.
Wow, you've got a thirst.
Look behind me. The bird in pink.
I've fucked her up the arse.
She loves to fuck.
She's only a little girl.
Cheers!
I've got nothing.
Here it is.
Is Cchepas here?
What's up with you?
Look at him.
How long is it since you were out?
It was at least 2 years ago.
Look at him now.
He looks like the fucking Dalai Lama.
Hrere.
Hi darling.
No, don't give him anything.
Let him suffer.
Look at him.
Now we can talk.
Do you want a drink?
Get Cchepa's stuff.
I'm going to the loo.
-Are you hungry for adventure, girls?
-How come? We know you're gay.
Your brother's an idiot.
Do you know that?
-Your brother's an idiot.
-Yeah.
Yeah, he sure is.
And how many kids do you have?
-How many kids do you have?
-Two.
-Where are they now?
-They've gone away.
They've gone up to the snow.
-Who with?
-With their mum.
-Why didn't you go with them?
-'cause I can't.
Why can't you?
Because I'm dying.
I'm dying of cancer.
PYRENEES IS BlUTlFUL
Mateo, my sweet?
Mateo.
kiddo...
Why are you all alone?
I wet myself.
Don't worry about that.
What happened?
Mamma punished me.
She left me here.
She went off with Ana.
They went up to the snow.
What have you done to your face?
I was very disobedient.
Daddy...
Let me explain.
-It was Ana's birthday and Mateo...
-Don't talk to me, Marambra.
It's good you're moving.
I'm really glad you're pissing off.
You hear that?
Goddamned pig.
You're a goddamned pig!
You can't even look at me, eh?
Give me the photo, Marambra.
His dad.
Tell him to be quiet.
Quieten him.
Sleep now, Mateo.
Daddy, Why is Ige living at our place?
'Cause he doesn't have any home of his own.
And he has a little kid.
-Can I answer?
-No, as I've already told you.
Where are the kids?
I followed them to school.
-Why didn't you wake me up?
-You slept like a log.
Ana said she knew the way
and Mateo thought it was OK.
What time is it?
I don't know, it must be one.
If you like, I can pick up the kids.
He went ballistic.
Liwei betrayed me.
Everything was his idea.
You know what sort of a guy he was.
He threw them in, 300 metres out to sea.
Shimuya swore
that the bodies sank to the bottom.
Liwei thought you'd betray us.
I was afraid too.
They've taken my family.
My daughter Suyin.
To top it all off, Liwei came
looking for me and cried.
This is insane.
What do you want me to do?
We can't stand here.
Get away from here and be quick about it.
-What do you want?
-You aren't innocent, Uxbal.
-What?
-Don't play dumb.
You gotta get it into your head.
My people don't squeal.
I promise you.
You gotta shut up anyone you know
who knows anything.
The news has shocked the whole country.
The latest we know is
that most of the dead are men-
-but among them were also found
two women and three children.
We warn that these images may disturb some viewers.
The search for bodies continues...
No, I don't know.
It's not certain.
No, it's not certain.
What? No.
Near the Chinese's warehouse.
I don't know.
One family or something.
Just a sec, there's someone at the door.
No, no, no, don't hang up.
What the hell are you doing here?
-I heard it right.
-Why didn't you say anything to me?
-Are we talking about the same thing?
-I dunno.
Are we talking about the same thing?
This is terrible.
Want a drink?
-Marambras purse?
-Leave it alone.
I don't understand.
Did you murder them, Uxbal?
-Fucking piece of shit.
-For chrissakes, Uxbal...
Fucking piece of shit.
He was totally hysterical and stood and cried.
What was I supposed to do?
Leave her out there?
This is partly your fault, Uxbal.
If I see you anywhere near
my wife or my children-
-under a kilometre away,
I swear on my mother-
-I'll kill you, you fucking piece of shit.
I can't move.
I feel like if I touched my neck-
-my head would fall off.
Calm down. Nothing's
gonna fall off.
If I close my eyes-
-the tanks are coming.
They scare  me.
I called you.
I rang you over and over.
I don't have what the children need.
I'm sorry I was nasty to Mateo.
I do what I can
to survive.
I want to be faithful to you.
But i also want to have a bit of fun ...
...as a whore.
Don't say that, Marambra.
I'm sorry.
I never knew
what I should give you.
I still don't know.
Come to think of it...
I've never known it
But we've hurt each other so much.
Take me on a holiday again.
At the clinic
they have to tie me...
Quiet.
Quiet. It'll be OK
It's going to be OK.
She is in the same house
where we visited her before.
Remember?
And she...
We must just let her rest.
-Take her hand?
-Yes.
She has 20 people
who take her hand.
She sent lots of kisses.
She loves you lots and lots.
-Can we say hello to her?
-Yes, of course darling.
But now we have to let her rest.
Make a wish, little lady.
Give me your hand.
-Don't shove it up your nose.
-Give me your hand.
What's that? A booger?
It's something you shall have
from your daddy.
Are you scared of it?
Do you promise?
-Are you frightened of it?
-Yes.
Shouldn't we have the cake now?
Sit down , Ige.
OK...
The first thing we must do...
Mateo, don't be disgusting.
...is to eat
yummy chocolate cake.
The kids are so fond of you Ige.
You and Samuel.
You have a home here.
And you can stay as long as you want.
No, Uxbal.
I'm also fond of the children-
-but I'll save up some money
and then I'm going back.
This is no place for us.
Ekweme told me about...
Wait.
Here is enough for rent for a whole year-
-and much more.
All for the children.
Do you understand?
Take the money.
Take them.
Ige, please...
Can't you stay?
I need your help.
Take it now. Take it.
Goddamn...
What is it?
Nothing.
-Why aren't you in school?
-Don't lie to me Daddy.
Come here.
Does your brother know anything about this?
You can't leave us.
I won't.
Look in my eyes.
Look at my face.
Promise to remember me.
Don't forget me, Ana.
Don't forget me, my darling.
'Bye.
Ige?
yes, it's me.
I'm back.
Daddy, are you OK?
Yes, darling.
Does it hurt?
No.
I can't sleep. Light...
The ring looks funny on your hand.
Can I look at it?
-Is it real?
-Yes.
It was from my daddy to my mummy.
And why have you got it?
To...
...your grandfather gave it
to your grandmother...
...before he left Spain.
She was pregnant and expecting me...
...and she never saw him again.
It's lovely. I never thought
I'd touch a real diamond.
-Can I try it on?
-Yes.
-It's yours now darling.
-Really?
Mummy always wore it
on this finger.
She said it wasn't real.
Your mother never heard the sound.
What sound?
The sound of the sea.